Igor Polajžer

ID: IE0665545

Date of birth: 22/07/2003

Place of birth: Maribor, Slovenia

Nationality: Slovenian

CONTACT

Gradišča 83,2282 Cirkulane, Slovenia(Home)

polajzerigor@gmail.com

(+386) 070495374

https://igorpolajzer.com/

in <u>Igor Polajžer</u>



ABOUT ME

I am Igor Polajžer, a dedicated 21-year-old student pursuing a degree in Computer Science at the Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (FERI) in Maribor. Currently in my third and also last year of studies, I exhibit a strong work ethic and a relentless drive to acquire new skills and experiences within the tech industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/08/2023 - 09/2023 Maribor, Slovenia

Software engineer Skylabs d.o.o

At Skylabs d.o.o, I was responsible for transforming C++ libraries into Pythoncompatible modules by creating wrappers. Additionally, I developed a RESTful API to provide easy access to these libraries. My role involved the entire development lifecycle, from concept to deployment. Through this experience, I enhanced my skills in C++, Python, web development and project managment gaining valuable expertise in software integration and API design

01/08/2024 - CURRENT Ljubljana, Slovenia

Programmer Setronica d.o.o

At Setronica, I ensure the quality of large language models (LLMs) by reviewing and evaluating Al-generated outputs, assessing their accuracy, and providing detailed feedback to enhance model performance. I prepare datasets for AI training, ensuring high-quality inputs for model development. Additionally, I work in a diverse, multicultural environment, collaborating with professionals from different nationalities to refine AI solutions and optimize model outputs.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/09/2018 - 24/06/2024 Ptuj, Slovenia

Technic of mechatronics Electrical and Computer School Ptuj

Website https://elektro.scptuj.si/ | Level in EQF EQF level 4

01/10/2022 - CURRENT Maribor, Slovenia

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technology
Engineering The Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computer

Website https://feri.um.si/ | Level in EQF EQF level 6

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Slovenian

Other language(s):

English

Listening C1Spoken production C1Reading C2Spoken interaction C1

Writing C1

German

Listening A1 Spoken production A1
Reading A1 Spoken interaction A1

Writing A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

C | C++ | C# | Java | LibGdx | Kotlin | Jetpack Compose | Python | Flask | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Node.js | MERN Stack (MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS) | Lamp Stack (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP) | SQL | Docker/Docker Hub | Git/Github | Blender | Microsoft (Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Outlook) | Gim p